Themis Tsiligkoudis

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Profile

Detail-oriented and self-driven .NET Developer with a track record in developing and implementing web-based solutions, maintaining, and updating web applications, and improving the whole programming process. With a deep passion for technology, extensive technological expertise, and well-developed teamwork abilities.

Employment History

Software Developer | Classter

OCTOMBER 2022 — PRESENT

Joined the development team for the company's main product. Resolving bugs and providing new features daily for both front and backend development.

- Used ASP.NET, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript to design and develop new features for company's main product.
- Trouble-Shot and fixed any threads and Bugs.
- Maintained and refactored old features using more advanced technics.
- Over 300 Azure work items solved including backlogs and bugs.

Software Developer & Technical Support Professional | Classter

MARCH 2021 — OCTOMBER 2022

Provided customer support for the company's main product. Tested every possible scenario before informing the development department about an issue. Gain good knowledge of database management and scripting through daily customer issues and demands. Created several reports with SSRS. 3000+ support cases resolved.

- 2000+ cases created on azure (either for bugs or product backlogs).
- 500+ azure cases resolved (either migration issues or report bugs).
- 400+ reports created or made further adjustments.
- 250+ scripts created by me to solve customer issues or demands.
- Good Experience in debugging and finding the source of the problem.
- Good Experience regarding external providers and third-party integrations and APIs.

Military Trooper

SEPTEMBER 2020 — MAY 2021

Joined Military. Due to my Computer Science degree, they had me working in the office where we had a lot of problems to address daily.

- Updated a program written in Excel VBA to automatically assign soldiers in their daily jobs.
- Updated a program to automatically count the military leaves of all soldiers.
- Archived all soldier files and sorted them by years.
- Was responsible of interviewing the newcomers.
- Assisted in fixing several electronics that had issues.

Details

Antiochias 3, Kavala, 65404, Greece +306943444650 themtsil@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Greek

DRIVING LICENSE

A1 - B

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

24/05/1996 Kavala, Greece

Social Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Github

Digital Resume

Programming skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

JQuery

Responsive Design

Cross Browser Development

SQL

C#

Rest API

Entity Framework

ASP.NET MVC

ASP.NET Maui

ASP.NET Core

C++

Software Developer & Technical Staff | Classter Internship

JULY 2020 — AUGUST 2020

Started my Internship in Classter. Learned a lot of new skills and expended my horizon

- Software Testing.
- Database documentation.
- Custom CSS themes for their base product.
- Assisted in building the Company's new Network infrastructure.

Education

Diploma in Electrical and Computer Engineering, Democritus University of Thrace, Xanthi

SEPTEMBER 2014 — JUNE 2021

Qualified as Integrated Master with 300 ECTS and 7.03 / 10 Overall grade

High school, 2nd, Kavala

SEPTEMBER 2011 — JULY 2014

Certifications

Life-Skills Shaping Life and Social Entrepreneurs, Xanthi (British council)

Renewable Energy Sources and Sustainability and Development, Xanthi (MEDILAB and ESTIEMLG at states of program REUNI)

DECEMBER 2016

Skills & Qualifications

- **✓** Experience with front & backend development.
- **✓** Good knowledge in API & Database Design.
- Experience with problem solving.
- **✓** Experience with customer support.
- **✓** Experience with Report creation (SSRS).
- ✓ Ability and speed of learning
- **✓** Consistency
- **✓** Conflict resolution
- **✓** Cooperation
- ✓ Pleasant and positive spirit

Github Projects

EShop MVC

EShop Core

EShop API

EShop Mobile App

HangMan

SignalR Server

HangMan Mobile app

Library

Digital Resume

Arduino GPS GSM Device

Arduino Camera Snapshot

Live Web Apps

EShop

EShop API

Digital-Resume

<u>HangMan</u>

SignalR Server

Foreign Languages

Certificate of competency in English